<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">


    <TextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:text="LIST"
        android:textSize="30dp" />

    <androidx.coordinatorlayout.widget.CoordinatorLayout
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <com.fiberthemax.youtubelikelayout.TopLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:background="#ff0000">

            <ImageView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="250dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:scaleType="centerCrop"
                android:src="@drawable/top_image" />
        </com.fiberthemax.youtubelikelayout.TopLayout>

        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:background="@color/black"
            app:layout_behavior="com.fiberthemax.youtubelikelayout.BottomViewBehavior">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:padding="10dp"
                android:text="The Martian is a 2015 science fiction film directed by Ridley Scott and starring Matt Damon. Drew Goddard adapted the screenplay from the 2011 novel The Martian by Andy Weir. The film depicts an astronaut's lone struggle to survive on Mars after being left behind and the efforts of NASA to rescue him and bring him home to Earth. It also stars Jessica Chastain, Kristen Wiig, Jeff Daniels, Michael Peña, Sean Bean, Kate Mara, Sebastian Stan, Aksel Hennie, Mackenzie Davis, Benedict Wong, Donald Glover, Chen Shu, Eddy Ko, and Chiwetel Ejiofor.

Produced through 20th Century Fox, the film is a coproduction of the United Kingdom and the United States. Producer Simon Kinberg began developing the film after Fox optioned the novel in March 2013, which Drew Goddard adapted into a screenplay and was initially attached to direct, but the film did not move forward. Ridley Scott replaced Goddard as director, and with Damon in place as the main character, production was approved. Filming began in November 2014 and lasted approximately seventy days. Twenty sets were built on one of the largest sound stages in the world in Budapest, Hungary. Wadi Rum in Jordan was also used for exterior filming.

The film premiered at the 2015 Toronto International Film Festival on September 11, 2015, while the London premiere was held on September 24, 2015. The film was released in the United Kingdom on September 30, 2015, and in the United States on October 2, 2015, in 2D, 3D, IMAX 3D and 4DX.[5] It received positive reviews and grossed over $630 million worldwide, becoming Scott's highest-grossing film to date, as well as the 10th-highest-grossing film of 2015. The Martian received praise for its direction, visual effects, musical score, screenplay, scientific accuracy, and likability, largely due to Damon's performance. It received several accolades, including the Golden Globe Award for Best Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy, seven nominations at the 88th Academy Awards, including Best Picture and Best Adapted Screenplay for Goddard, and the 2016 long form Hugo Award for Best Dramatic Presentation. Damon won the Golden Globe Award for Best Actor – Motion Picture Musical or Comedy and was nominated for several awards including the Academy Award for Best Actor, the BAFTA Award for Best Actor in a Leading Role, and the Critics' Choice Award for Best Actor."
                android:textColor="@color/white"
                android:textSize="20dp" />
        </ScrollView>

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:background="@color/black"
            android:gravity="end|center_vertical"
            app:layout_behavior="com.fiberthemax.youtubelikelayout.SideViewBehavior">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="0dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="10dp"
                android:layout_weight="1"
                android:text="Martian"
                android:textColor="@color/white" />

            <ImageButton
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:background="?android:selectableItemBackground"
                android:clickable="true"
                android:focusable="true"
                android:padding="10dp"
                android:src="@drawable/ic_baseline_share_24"
                app:tint="@color/white" />

            <ImageButton
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:background="?android:selectableItemBackground"
                android:clickable="true"
                android:focusable="true"
                android:padding="10dp"
                android:src="@drawable/ic_baseline_info_24"
                app:tint="@color/white" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </androidx.coordinatorlayout.widget.CoordinatorLayout>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>